Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Files 5808
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files
1973-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seidenberg, Jacob
5808
19.11 cubic feet
19.1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3126349
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 29, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Dr. Jacob Seidenberg (1914-1996) was a government official who specialized in labor arbitration and non-discrimination contracts, and wrote extensively on labor law and negotiations. He graduated from Temple University in 1937 and received a law degree from the University of Pennsylvania Law School in 1941. During the 1940s he was an attorney with the U.S. War Department, the National War Labor Board and the National Wage Stabilization Board. In 1948 he went to graduate school at Cornell University, from which he earned his Ph.D. in industrial and labor relations in 1951. In 1951 he joined the staff of the President's Committee on Government Contract Compliance. The Committee was abolished by President Dwight D. Eisenhower in August 1953 by Executive Order 10479 and was succeeded by the President's Committee on Government Contracts. Seidenberg was appointed Executive Director of the new committee and served until January 1960 when he resigned to become a full-time labor arbitrator. The Committee was responsible for enforcing non-discrimination clauses in government contracts, worked with private businesses to help them overcome job discrimination, and developed educational programs against ethnic and racial discrimination. The chairman was Vice President Richard Nixon, and the vice chairman was Secretary of Labor James P. Mitchell. In later years Seidenberg served on a number of boards of inquiry involving labor disputes. From 1970 to 1975 he was chairman of the Federal Services Impasses Panel which settled deadlocks in federal labor negotiations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5031 A&B: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5032: Jacob Seidenberg Injunction Study 5175: Jacob Seidenberg Taft-Hartley Maritime Dispute Records 5194: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Files 5217: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Case Files 5229: Jacob Seidenberg Additional records 5468: Jacob Seidenberg Arbitration files 5519: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5571: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5605: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5635: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5666: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5706: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5756: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5773: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5808: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5900: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5935: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5953: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5988: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial--United States--Sources.; Seidenberg, Jacob.
3126349
- Acme Markets, Inc., 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  12/11/84 - 6/17/86. Arbitration procedure, discipline, suspension.
- American Federation of Teachers Staff Union, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  7/1/87 - 7/2/87. Termination of employment.
- American Postal Workers, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  10/11/84 - 6/14/85. Working conditions.
- American Postal Workers, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  9/18/84 - 8/21/85. Contracting out, overtime, assignment of jobs.
- American Technology Corp., 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  9/17/85 - 6/1/87. Termination of employment.
- Annapolis Hilton, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  9/7/84 - 12/21/84. Discipline.
- Avco Aero structures Division, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  3/25/85 -4/22/85. Correspondence/resolved case.
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway Co., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  10/15/86 - 11/1/86. Duty to bargain, seniority.
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway Co., 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  4/27/84 - 1/5/85. Rates of pay, premium pay, compensation.
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway Co., 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  3/19/86 - 6/2/87. Duty to bargain.
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway Co., 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  3/21/84 - 2/21/85. Reinstatement, seniority, premium pay, rates of pay.
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway Co. Santa Fe. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Formal investigation & exhibits. Volume I of III. Termination of employment, work rules, assignment of jobs.
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway Co. Santa Fe. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Formal investigation. Volume II of III. Issues see F.F. 12. Volume III of III is in Box 2, F.F. 1
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway Co. Santa Fe. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Formal investigation Volume III of III.
- The Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co., Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  11/21/84 - 9/26/85. Termination of employment.
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co., Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  2/14/85 -2/14/86. Arbitrability, rates of pay.
- Boyertown Packaging Corp., 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  11/30/84 -10/10/85. Contracting out.
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  4/17/86. Reduction in force, contracting out, elimination of jobs, assignment of jobs.
- Boston & Maine Corp., 1974-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  8/14/74 - 12/9/85. Arbitration procedure, assignment of jobs, rates of pay, compensation.
- Burlington Northern Railroad Co., 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  9/10/85 -7/3/86. Promotion, seniority, rates of pay, assignment of jobs.
- Caesar's Boardwalk Regency, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  1/2/85 -5/18/85. Termination of employment.
- Calvert County Board of Education, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  8/5/85 -2/4/86. Assignment of jobs.
- Cambridge Wire Cloth Co., 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  11/13/86 - 7/19/87. Assignment of jobs, discrimination, seniority.
- Catalytic, Inc., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  4/7/87 - 9/23/87. Termination of jobs.
- Catalytic, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  5/1/86 & 1/8/87. Brief/substance abuse police.
- Catalytic, Inc., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  8/18/87. Termination of employment, work rules.
- Catalytic, Inc., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13A)
  6/4/87. Alcoholism/drug abuse, termination of employment: Research material on other similar cases and literature.
- Charles County School Board, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  2/19/85 -3/24/85. Reduction in force, rates of pay, compensation, incentive pay/incentive systems, lunch periods, assignment of jobs.
- Charlton Brothers Transportation Co., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  4/16/85 - 7/26/85. Termination of employment.
- Chicago & Northwestern Transportation Co., 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  11/4/85 - 2/24/87. Suspension, compensation, assignment of jobs, seniority, vacancy, premium pay.
- Chicago & Northwestern Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  5/21/86 - 7/22/86. Premium pay, rates of pay, assignment of jobs.
- Chicago & Northwestern Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  5/20/86 - 7/7/86. Premium pay, compensation, suspension, assignment of jobs.
- Chicago & Northwestern Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  5/20/86 - 7/8/86. Suspension, compensation, rates of pay, premium pay.
- Chicago & Northwestern Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  7/16/86 - 9/8/86. Suspension, compensation, rates of pay, premium pay.
- Chicago & Northwestern Transportation Co., 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  2/11/86 - 2/29/87. Seniority, contract interpretation.
- Chicago & Northwestern Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  9/9/86 - 12/29/86. Rates of pay, suspension, compensation, assignment of jobs, premium
- Chicago & Northwestern Transportation Co., 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  9/9/86 - 1/29/87. Premium pay, rates of pay, assignment of jobs & related cases.
- Chicago & Northwestern Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  5/20/86 - 7/24/86. Suspension, compensation.
- Churchill Distribution, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  3/1/83 - 4/27/86. Termination of employment.
- Claire Frock Co., Inc., 1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  1/7/87 - 6/5/87. Termination of employment.
- Community College of Philadelphia, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  6/12/85 -10/8/85. Termination of employment.
- Classified Municipal Employees Association, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  12/31/86-8/14/87. Union election, intra-union disputes.
- Classified Municipal Employees Association, Inc., 1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  12/86. Union election, intra - union disputes.
- Classified Municipal Employees Association, Inc., 1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  5/87. Union election, intra - union disputes.
- Classified Municipal Employees Association, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Transcripts, Volumes I - IV
- Conrail, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  11/30/87-1/17/88. Discipline, compensation, seniority.
- Conrail, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  3/3/88 - 4/28/88. Compensation, suspension, assignment of jobs, discipline, termination of employment, seniority.
- Conrail, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  3/3/88-3/17/88. Assignment of jobs, rates of pay, seniority, premium pay, bidding, holiday pay.
- Conrail, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  11/30/87-1/7/88. Assignment of jobs, premium pay, discipline, leaves of absence, seniority.
- Conrail, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  11/30/87-11/14/88. Premium pay, assignment of jobs.
- Conrail Discipline, compensation. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Conrail System docket #CR - 188. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Conrail System docket #CR - 201. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Conrail, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  5/19/87-6/18/87. Termination of employment, compensation.
- Conrail, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  5/19/87-7/27/87. Overtime, rates of pay, welfare fund, discipline, absences, termination of employment.
- Conrail, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  5/19/87-7/11/87. Overtime, assignment of jobs, termination of employment, reinstatement, discipline, compensation, vacancy.
- Conrail Reinstatement, compensation. Exhibits. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Conrail Exhibits. (Box 5, Folder 8)
- CSX Transportation Inc., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  4/14/88 - 5/28/88. Seniority, welfare fund, union security.
- CSX Transportation Inc., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  4/14/88 - 6/22/88. Union security, compensation.
- CSX Transportation Inc. Vacancy, assignment of jobs, rates of pay. (Box 5A, Folder 1)
- Delaware & Hudson Railway Co. 9/3/85 -12/2/85. Transfer, working conditions., 1985 (Box 5A, Folder 2)
- Delaware & Hudson Railway Co., 1985 (Box 5A, Folder 3)
  8/29/85. Rates of pay, resignation, transfer.
- Delaware & Hudson Railway Co., 1985 (Box 5A, Folder 4)
  8/29/85 -10/21/85. Transfer, rates of pay: Brief of the same issues.
- Delaware & Hudson Railway Co., 1985 (Box 5A, Folder 5)
  8/29/85 -10/22/85. Assignment of jobs, termination of employment, termination of operation: Transcript.
- Dimensions Health Corp., 1987 (Box 5A, Folder 6)
  5/22/87 - 7/8/87. Suspension.
- District of Columbia Board of Education, 1984-1985 (Box 5A, Folder 7)
  7/18/84 - 4/29/85. Termination of employment, reinstatement.
- District of Columbia Public Schools, 1985-1986 (Box 5A, Folder 8)
  11/6/85 -7/1/86. Suspension, termination of employment, reinstatement, compensation.
- District of Columbia Public Schools, 1985-1986 (Box 5A, Folder 9)
  7/18/85 -8/11 /86. Termination of employment, compensation.
- District of Columbia Public Schools, 1985-1987 (Box 5A, Folder 10)
  9/11/85 -9/23/87. Termination of employment, alcoholism/drug abuse, discipline.
- ** Transcript & black binder are between these two files (Box 6)
- District of Columbia Metropolitan Police Department, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  3/4/86 - 6/24/86. Improper personal conduct, theft, termination of employment.
- District of Columbia Metropolitan Police Department, 1973-1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  3/6/73-7/16/85. Suspension, improper personal conduct, fights & altercations.
- District of Columbia Metropolitan Police Department, 1983-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  5/5/83 - 1/8/87. Termination of employment, arbitration procedure, transfers.
- Dupont Company, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  1/23/86 - 6/12/86. Termination of employment, fights & altercations.
- Eastern Airlines & Local 553, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  4/12/86 -6/9/86. Termination of employment, medical release and physical exams.
- Eastern Airlines & Local 553, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  9/4/86 -12/9/86. Termination of employment.
- Federation of Professional Athletes, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  11/5/84 -10/14/85. Promotions, seniority.
- Georgetown University, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  7/21/86 - 6/2/87. Compensation, rates of pay.
- Georgetown University, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  1/11/85 - 6/6/85. Termination of employment, fights & altercations.
- Georgetown University, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  9/13/84 - 3/8/85. Arbitrability, assignment of jobs.
- Giant Food, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  11/24/86-3/20/87. Vacancy, hiring, vacation/vacation pay.
- M.S. GinnCo., 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  9/13/85-10/31/86. Bargaining unit, supervisory employees, termination of employment.
- Globe Battery Division, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  2/2/83 - 10/3/83. Termination of employment, contract interpretation.
- Gray Drug Fair - Metropolitan Guild, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  6/21/87. Just a canceled case.
- Group Health, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  3/2/86 - 4/7/87. Transfer.
- Harford County Public Schools, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  10/11/84 -2/11/85. Reduction in force, elimination of jobs.
- Hermetite Division - Mindet Industry, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  11/20/86 -4/21/87. Holiday/holiday pay.
- Harrah's Marina Hotel & Casino, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  11 /16/85. Canceled case.
- Henson Aviation, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  5/13/87-9/14/87. Canceled case.
- J.F.K. Center for the Performing Arts, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  1 /11 /84 -2/19/86. Termination of employment, contract interpretation.
- J.F.K. Center for the Performing Arts, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  4/2/85 -7/1/85. Severance pay.
- Koppers Co., 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  2/1/85-3/19/85. Canceled case.
- Kolker Poultry Co., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  4/10/87 - 5/1/87. Termination of employment, suspension.
- Lenox China, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  11/13/86 - 4/20/87. Termination of employment, improper personal conduct, back pay.
- Loomis Armored, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  10/1/84 - 5/20/85. Termination of employment.
- M & L Dessert Corporation, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  2/14/86 - 9/18/86. Contract interpretation.
- Macke Building Maintenance Corp., 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  7/9/85 -1/23/86. Arbitrability, recall, assignment of jobs, vacation pay.
- Case Maine Central, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  6/10/85- 11/12/85. Working conditions.
- Missouri - Kansas - Texas Railroad Co., 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  10/18/83 - 3/25/85. Contract interpretation, termination of employment, reinstatement, back pay, seniority.
- Mount Vernon Care Center, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  11 /16/84 -4/22/85. Termination of employment.
- National Education Services, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  4/15/85 -12/9/85. Arbitration procedure, grievance & procedure, bargaining unit.
- National Railroad Passenger Corp., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  3/5/86 -12/5/86. Termination of employment, seniority, back pay, reinstatement, discipline, suspension.
- National Railroad Passenger Corp., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  5/13/86 -9/11/86. Assignment of jobs, compensation.
- Public Law Board & New Jersey Transit Rail, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  5/13/85 - 6/17/85. Assignment of jobs, contracting out, job classification, compensation.
- Public Law Board & New Jersey Transit Rail, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  5/28/85 - 9/24/85. Contracting out, reinstatement, termination of employment.
- Ocean One Mall, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  3/20/85 - 4/23/85. Termination of employment.
- Owens - Illinois Co., Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  9/26/85 - 1/9/86. Termination of employment.
- Pan Am World Airways, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  4/6/85-12/2/85. Assignment of jobs, compensation, rates of pay.
- Penna Power & Light Co., 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  11/8/84 - 12/6/85. Canceled case.
- Philadelphia Gas Works, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  3/18/85 - 6/12/85. Contracting out, bargaining unit.
- Printing Industries (Negative Corp.), 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  5/1/86 -7/2/86. Contract interpretation, training, assignment of jobs.
- Purolator Armored, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  1/25/85-2/25/85. Termination of employment.
- Purity Grap, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  12/20/85 - 1/20/86. Termination of employment.
- Quality Foods, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  4/7/87 - 7/5/87. Termination of employment.
- Raytheon Service, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  12/12/84 - 2/19/85. Termination of employment.
- RCA, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  1/29/86-4/2/86. Termination of employment: transcripts included.
- Republic Airlines, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  2/6/84 - 2/26/86. Discipline, grievance & procedure.
- Republic Airlines, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  12/30/85- 10/14/86. Arbitrability, discipline.
- Resorts International, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  4/20/80 - 4/12/86. Bumping, seniority, welfare fund, premium pay, holiday, grievance/arbitration procedure, rates of pay.
- Resorts International, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  2/24/87 - 7/20/87. Termination of employment.
- Reynolds Metal Co., 1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  1/16/87-4/7/87. Correspondence: Cancellation.
- Ris Paper Co., 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  12/19/86 - 5/27/87. Termination of employment, vacancy.
- Rockingham Poultry, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  7/21/87. Transcripts//reinstatement.
- St. Louis Southwestern Railroad Co., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  2/12/86 -4/30/86. Overtime, assignment of jobs, rates of pay, compensation.
- St. Louis Southwestern Railroad Co. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Compensation, rates of pay, assignment of jobs, premium pay.
- St. Louis Southwestern Railroad Co., 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  3/21/83 -2/23/86. Reinstatement, compensation, suspension.
- St. Louis Southwestern Railroad Co. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  Assignment of jobs//exhibits.
- St. Louis Southwestern Railroad Co., 1977-1986 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  11/16/77 -6/2/86. Rates of pay, compensation, reinstatement, suspension.
- St. Mary's County Board of Education, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  3/19/86 - 6/29/86. Rates of pay, overtime, fringe benefits.
- Sanborn's Motor Express Co., 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  10/18/85 -12/23/85. Termination of employment.
- Singer Corp., 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  12/20/84 - 5/4/85. Layoff.
- Singer Corp., 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  11/19/84-5/16/85. Promotion, seniority.
- Sperry Corp., 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  6/26/84 - 10/28/85. Termination of employment.
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  2/24/86 - 9/22/86. Suspension, discipline.
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  6/7/85 - 11/2/85. Assignment of jobs, dishonesty.
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  6/18/85 - 2/18/86. Rates of pay, duty to bargain.
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  11/18/86. Termination of employment: Transcript & agreement.
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  7/24/86 - 3/11/88. Welfare fund.
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  12/27/86-9/15/87. Termination of employment, alcoholism/drug abuse & some related cases.
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  8/26/86-9/15/87. Termination of employment, negligence & carelessness.
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  10/28/86 - 9/15/87. Termination of employment.
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  8/21/86 - 2/25/87. Union security, bargaining unit.
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  8/20/86 - 12/29/86. Termination of employment, absences.
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transit Authority, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  11/3/86 - 4/17/87. Suspension, discipline.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1987 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  ^12^1^7 -7/31/87. Suspension, compensation, termination of employment.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  12/2/87 -2/11/88. Rates of pay, premium pay, assignment of jobs.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  8/9/85 -9/9/86. Assignment of jobs, rates of pay, medical release/physical exams, vacancy, transfer, reinstatement, termination of employment, premium pay, call-in, suspension, leaves of absence.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1985 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  2/12/85 -5/10/85. Compensation.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  10/2/86. Formal investigation of employees.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  Termination of employment, rates of pay, seniority, vacation pay, compensation.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1987 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  11/3/87 -12/18/87. Overtime, premium pay, assignment of jobs.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  1/12/87 -4/17/87. Suspension: copy of formal investigation.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  2/11/86 -6/2/86. Assignment of jobs, negligence & carelessness.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  2/11/86 -6/5/86. Compensation, assignment of jobs, premium pay// formal investigation report.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  2/11 /86 -5/5/86. Overtime, vacancy, assignment of jobs.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  8/18/83 -3/28/84. Reinstatement, compensation, discipline, vacancy, seniority.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  6/16/88 -7/26/88. Suspension, compensation, vacation.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  5/21/88 -7/26/88. Assignment of jobs, compensation, suspension.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  6/15/88. Suspension.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  5/13/88 -5/18/88. Compensation, negligence & carelessness, suspension.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  6/11/88 -7/17/88. Suspension.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  3/12/86 -5/28/86. Overtime, call-in, arbitration procedure, vacation, vacancy, compensation.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  12/13/84 -3/11 /86. Compensation, medical release/physical exams, assignment of jobs, rates of pay, layoff.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  11/1/84 -5/30/86. Suspension, compensation, vacation, arbitration procedure, termination of employment, assignment of jobs.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  3/11/86 -4/15/86. Termination of employment, leaves of absence, reinstatement, insubordination, assignment of jobs, suspension, compensation.
- Steamship Trade Association, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  2/6/87 -4/10/87. Assignment of jobs.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1985 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  5/27/55. Compensation, reinstatement, back pay.
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  1/12/87. Suspension, reinstatement, assignment of jobs, termination of employment, discrimination.